"Double Helix"
"الحلزون المزدوج"
I'm... I'm trying to be nice.
أنا... أنا أحاول أن أكون لطيفاً.
Don't... don't push your luck.
لا... لا تجازف.
Believe it or not,
صدق أو لا تصدق،
today I'll...
اليوم سأفعل...
What... what are you doing?
ماذا... ماذا تفعل؟
I'll say it again.
سأقولها مرة أخرى.
My performance contract
عقد الأداء الخاص بي
only specifies the setlist and duration.
يحدد فقط قائمة الأغاني والمدة.
It doesn't include taking requests.
ولا يشمل ذلك تلقي الطلبات.
Also, don't touch me without permission.
أيضًا، لا تلمسني بدون إذن.
It's common courtesy.
هذا من باب المجاملة.
Guys,
شباب،
let's drink.
هيا نشرب.
Sorry about that, everyone.
أعتذر عن ذلك يا جماعة.
Sorry for the disturbance.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج.
Next, I'd like to play a song for you all.
بعد ذلك، أود أن أعزف لكم أغنية.
It's one I wrote myself.
إنها أغنية كتبتها بنفسي.
Alright! Alright! Alright!
حسناً! حسناً! حسناً!
Let me treat you to a late-night snack.
دعني أقدم لك وجبة خفيفة في وقت متأخر من الليل.
I've told you many times.
لقد أخبرتك بذلك مرات عديدة.
I don't want to have anything to do with you.
لا أريد أن يكون لي أي علاقة بك.
So it's useless for you to keep pestering me.
لذا من غير المجدي أن تستمر في إزعاجي.
It's just a meal.
إنها مجرد وجبة.
I'm not asking for your hand in marriage.
أنا لا أطلب يدك للزواج.
Move.
يتحرك.
What do you want to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
(Episode 3: Stolen Happiness, I'm Willing)
(الحلقة 3: السعادة المسروقة، أنا مستعد)
Yichen.
ييتشن.
Um...
واحد...
Do you have any plans after graduation?
هل لديك أي خطط بعد التخرج؟
If all goes well, I'll probably stay here for now.
إذا سارت الأمور على ما يرام، فسأبقى هنا على الأرجح في الوقت الحالي.
My younger brother got into school here two years ago.
التحق أخي الأصغر بالمدرسة هنا قبل عامين.
This way, it's easier to look after him.
وبهذه الطريقة، يصبح الاعتناء به أسهل.
Have you ever thought about
هل فكرت يوماً في
checking out my family's company?
هل أتحقق من شركة عائلتي؟
I heard my dad say there's a position that's perfect for you.
سمعت والدي يقول إن هناك وظيفة مثالية لك.
Xiao Chen, come back quickly.
شياو تشن، عد بسرعة.
Your dad is dying.
والدك يحتضر.
Yichen.
ييتشن.
Dad's death was so sudden.
كانت وفاة أبي مفاجئة للغاية.
We were consumed by the terrible news,
لقد استبدّ بنا الخبر المروع،
drowning in sorrow,
غارق في الحزن،
unable to save ourselves.
عاجزون عن إنقاذ أنفسنا.
Bro.
أخ.
Are you still
هل ما زلت
trying to contact Lu Feng?
هل تحاول الاتصال بلو فنغ؟
Let me introduce you.
دعني أقدمك.
Your fiancée.
خطيبتك.
Whose?
لمن؟
The youngest daughter of the Lancheng real estate tycoon.
الابنة الصغرى لقطب العقارات في لانشنغ.
She's your age.
هي في سنك.
Our family's new internet company in Lancheng
شركة الإنترنت الجديدة لعائلتنا في لانشنغ
needs their support.
يحتاج إلى دعمهم.
What does that have to do with me?
ما علاقة ذلك بي؟
Dad said if you do what you're told and get engaged to her,
قال أبي: إذا فعلت ما يُطلب منك وخطبتها،
our company in Lancheng will be yours to manage.
ستكون شركتكم في لانشنغ تحت إدارتكم.
Tell her to get lost.
قل لها أن ترحل.
Lu Feng.
لو فنغ.
It's another way of saying,
إنها طريقة أخرى للقول،
you can fly back home.
يمكنك العودة إلى الوطن بالطائرة.
In the Chinese-American community,
في المجتمع الصيني الأمريكي،
Lu Feng, the second son of a famous entrepreneur,
لو فنغ، الابن الثاني لرجل أعمال شهير،
is twenty-four years old.
يبلغ من العمر أربعة وعشرين عاماً.
He and a well-known designer
هو ومصمم مشهور
suddenly announced their engagement recently.
أعلنوا خطوبتهم فجأة مؤخراً.
It's said they fell in love at first sight.
يقال إنهم وقعوا في الحب من النظرة الأولى.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Bro.
أخ.
He's not worth your grief. Forget him.
لا يستحق حزنك. انسيه.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
He forgot long ago.
لقد نسي ذلك منذ زمن بعيد.
He's cured.
لقد شُفي.
He can marry a woman now.
بإمكانه الزواج من امرأة الآن.
Too bad I'm not as capable as him.
يا للأسف، أنا لستُ بمثل كفاءته.
To forget so completely.
أن أنسى كل هذا النسيان.
Bro.
أخ.
Let me take you somewhere, okay?
دعني آخذك إلى مكان ما، حسناً؟
Where?
أين؟
You'll see when we get there.
سترى ذلك عندما نصل إلى هناك.
Two beers.
بيرة واحدة.
Bro, sit.
يا أخي، اجلس.
It's my treat today.
اليوم سأدفع ثمنها بنفسي.
Let's drink our hearts out. We're not leaving till we're drunk.
فلنشرب حتى الثمالة. لن نغادر حتى نثمل.
Okay.
تمام.
Bro, I'm going to the restroom.
يا أخي، أنا ذاهب إلى دورة المياه.
Yichen.
ييتشن.
You are...?
أنت...؟
Xiao Chen.
شياو تشن.
Lu Feng.
لو فنغ.
Lu Feng... Bro...
لو فنغ...يا أخي...
I'm not Lu Feng.
أنا لست لو فنغ.
Bro.
أخ.
Lu Feng.
لو فنغ.
Bro, don't be like this.
يا أخي، لا تكن هكذا.
You have an older brother?
هل لديك أخ أكبر؟
What's wrong with him?
ما به؟
It's like he's been through some kind of trauma.
يبدو الأمر كما لو أنه مرّ بنوع من الصدمة.
Qin Lang.
تشين لانج.
You like men, right?
أنتِ تحبين الرجال، أليس كذلك؟
To avoid any unnecessary misunderstandings,
لتجنب أي سوء فهم غير ضروري،
let me reiterate.
دعني أكرر.
You're the only one I like.
أنت الشخص الوحيد الذي يعجبني.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
But I don't like men.
لكنني لا أحب الرجال.
And I certainly don't like you.
وأنا بالتأكيد لا أحبك.
You just saw him.
لقد رأيته للتو.
My brother and I look quite alike, don't we?
أنا وأخي متشابهان إلى حد كبير، أليس كذلك؟
So,
لذا،
why don't you try liking my brother instead?
لماذا لا تحاول أن تحب أخي بدلاً من ذلك؟
Do you have any idea what you're saying?
هل لديك أدنى فكرة عما تقوله؟
My brother has been through a lot.
لقد مرّ أخي بالكثير.
He... fell in love with an irresponsible and selfish man.
لقد وقع في حب رجل غير مسؤول وأناني.
That guy just left back then without a word.
لقد غادر ذلك الرجل حينها دون أن ينبس ببنت شفة.
And now, that guy is suddenly getting married.
والآن، هذا الرجل سيتزوج فجأة.
My brother keeps saying he doesn't care,
أخي يكرر أنه لا يبالي،
but I know he hasn't forgotten for a single day.
لكنني أعلم أنه لم ينسَ ولو ليوم واحد.
Everyone says
الجميع يقول
the best way to get over a relationship
أفضل طريقة لتجاوز علاقة عاطفية
is to start a new one.
هو البدء بواحدة جديدة.
So, Qin Lang,
لذلك، تشين لانغ،
why don't you try dating my brother?
لماذا لا تحاولين مواعدة أخي؟
So this is your answer to me.
إذن هذا هو جوابك لي.
Fine.
بخير.
I'm not the shameless type
أنا لست من النوع الذي لا يخجل
who'll cling to you no matter what.
من سيتشبث بك مهما حدث.
As for your brother...
أما بالنسبة لأخيك...
he's not bad.
إنه ليس سيئاً.
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
As for you,
أما أنت،
do as you please.
افعل ما يحلو لك.
Okay.
تمام.
Xiao Chen.
شياو تشن.
Lu Feng.
لو فنغ.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
You are...?
أنت...؟
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
you had too much to drink at my bar.
لقد شربت أكثر من اللازم في حانتي.
You don't remember?
ألا تتذكر؟
Um...
واحد...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
No, I mean...
لا، أقصد...
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
I helped you
لقد ساعدتك
for a reason.
لسبب وجيه.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
I fell in love with you at first sight.
لقد وقعت في حبك من النظرة الأولى.
Could you give me a chance
هل يمكنك أن تمنحني فرصة؟
for us to get to know each other?
لكي نتعرف على بعضنا البعض؟
Eat.
يأكل.
That day,
في ذلك اليوم،
I didn't reject Qin Lang.
لم أرفض تشين لانغ.
I was in too much pain.
كنت أتألم بشدة.
I needed something new
كنت بحاجة إلى شيء جديد
to distract myself from Lu Feng.
لأشغل نفسي عن لو فنغ.
"Your brother loves my cooking."
"أخوك يحب طعامي."
My relationship with Qin Lang
علاقتي مع تشين لانغ
started inexplicably like that.
بدأ الأمر بشكل غير مفهوم.
Most of the time, we just talked.
في معظم الأوقات، كنا نتحدث فقط.
[He's complaining about being left on read]
[إنه يشتكي من تجاهل رسائله]
Qin Lang is a great guy.
تشين لانغ رجل رائع.
Considerate and gentle.
مراعٍ ولطيف.
We really clicked.
لقد انسجمنا تماماً.
Like old friends who've known each other for a long time.
مثل الأصدقاء القدامى الذين يعرفون بعضهم البعض منذ زمن طويل.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Time to cut the cake.
حان وقت تقطيع الكعكة.
Yichen.
ييتشن.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
This piece is for you.
هذه القطعة مخصصة لك.
It has the almonds you like.
يحتوي على اللوز الذي تحبه.
I specifically asked Shen Chao to order it.
طلبتُ تحديداً من شين تشاو أن يطلبها.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
But...
لكن...
I don't like almonds.
أنا لا أحب اللوز.
He does, though.
لكنه يفعل ذلك.
Thanks, bro.
شكراً يا أخي.
Delicious.
لذيذ.
Get in.
أدخل.
Bro, get in the car.
يا أخي، اركب السيارة.
Aren't you coming with us?
ألن تأتي معنا؟
I made plans with a friend.
لقد رتبت موعداً مع صديق.
We're pulling an all-nighter playing games at his place.
سنقضي الليلة بأكملها نلعب الألعاب في منزله.
It's not on the way.
إنها ليست في الطريق.
You get in, too.
يمكنك الدخول أيضاً.
I'll take your brother home first,
سآخذ أخاك إلى المنزل أولاً،
and then I'll take you to your friend's place.
وبعد ذلك سآخذك إلى منزل صديقك.
Get in, bro.
ادخل يا أخي.
As for you,
أما أنت،
you're just responsible for getting my brother
أنت مسؤول فقط عن إحضار أخي
back to school safely.
العودة إلى المدرسة بأمان.
Go on.
هيا.
Go on, don't drag your feet.
هيا، لا تتردد.
Your brother is so good to you.
أخوك يعاملك بلطف شديد.
He can't bear to see anyone hurt you.
لا يطيق أن يرى أي شخص يؤذيك.
But he has no problem hurting others.
لكن ليس لديه مشكلة في إيذاء الآخرين.
Including himself.
بما في ذلك نفسه.
Qin Lang.
تشين لانج.
Why are you suddenly saying this?
لماذا تقول هذا فجأة؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I just saw how close you and your brother are.
لقد رأيت للتو مدى قربك أنت وأخوك.
And it got me thinking.
وهذا الأمر جعلني أفكر.
When are you planning to finish school?
متى تخطط لإنهاء دراستك؟
How's the job hunt going?
كيف تسير عملية البحث عن وظيفة؟
I'm considering a few decent companies.
أفكر في بعض الشركات الجيدة.
But I haven't decided yet.
لكنني لم أقرر بعد.
Take your time. Don't rush.
خذ وقتك. لا تتعجل.
Well, take care.
حسناً، اعتنِ بنفسك.
Okay.
تمام.
Qin Lang.
تشين لانج.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخّرك كل هذا الوقت؟
My bad.
خطأي.
I'm late.
أنا متأخر.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yi-chen.
يي تشن.
Don't stay out too late.
لا تسهر لوقت متأخر.
Text me when you get there.
أرسل لي رسالة نصية عندما تصل إلى هناك.
[He's making himself crash out looking up Lu Feng news on the internet]
[يحاول أن ينام وهو يبحث عن أخبار لو فنغ على الإنترنت]
[Conversation with his brother]
[محادثة مع شقيقه]
Why am I at your place?
لماذا أنا هنا عندكم؟
You drank too much.
لقد شربت كثيراً.
Shen Chao brought you back.
أعادك شين تشاو.
He didn't know where you live.
لم يكن يعرف أين تسكن.
Didn't you say...
ألم تقل...
you were going to a friend's to play video games?
كنت ذاهباً إلى منزل صديق للعب ألعاب الفيديو؟
How did you end up this drunk?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر إلى هذه الحالة من السكر؟
Stay out of it.
ابتعد عن هذا الأمر.
I could've stayed out of it before.
كان بإمكاني الابتعاد عن الأمر من قبل.
But not anymore.
لكن ليس بعد الآن.
After all, I'm dating your brother, aren't I?
على كل حال، أنا أواعد أخاك، أليس كذلك؟
Your brother cares about you so much.
أخوك يهتم بك كثيراً.
As your brother's boyfriend,
بصفتي صديق أخيك،
I have to love what he loves.
يجب أن أحب ما يحبه.
- Plus... - Get out.
- بالإضافة إلى ذلك... - اخرج.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you not happy that your brother and I are getting along?
ألا يسعدك أنني وأخاك على وفاق؟
Isn't this what you wanted me to do?
أليس هذا ما كنت تريدني أن أفعله؟
Shut up.
اسكت.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
اصمت، اصمت، اصمت!
Tell me. Am I not doing enough?
أخبرني، هل أنا لا أبذل ما يكفي؟
Or do you want me and your brother to be together forever?
أم تريدني أنا وأخوك أن نبقى معاً إلى الأبد؟
So you can watch us be all lovey-dovey every day?
إذن يمكنك أن تشاهدنا ونحن نعيش لحظات رومانسية كل يوم؟
Yi-chen.
يي تشن.
Ask yourself.
اسأل نفسك.
Is this really what you want?
هل هذا ما تريده حقاً؟
I'm begging you, don't say it. I'm begging you.
أرجوك، لا تقل ذلك. أرجوك.
Why are you crying?
لماذا تبكين؟
I thought you didn't like me.
ظننت أنك لا تحبني.
I don't!
أنا لا!
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
I never should have gone along with your nonsense from the start.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أوافق على هراءك منذ البداية.
Let's go tell your brother the truth.
هيا بنا نخبر أخاك بالحقيقة.
That we lied to him.
أننا كذبنا عليه.
Okay?
تمام؟
No.
لا.
My brother won't be able to take it.
لن يستطيع أخي تحمل ذلك.
He can't get hurt again.
لا يمكنه أن يتعرض للأذى مرة أخرى.
The longer we drag this out, the more he'll be hurt.
كلما طال أمد هذا الأمر ، زاد ألمه.
I don't just fall for any guy I see.
أنا لا أقع في حب أي رجل أراه.
The person I've liked from the very beginning has only ever been you.
الشخص الذي أحببته منذ البداية لم يكن سوى أنت.
Do you expect me to lie to your brother for the rest of my life?
هل تتوقع مني أن أكذب على أخيك طوال حياتي؟
Is that even possible?
هل هذا ممكن أصلاً؟
Is that fair to me?
هل هذا منصف لي؟
Is that fair to your brother?
هل هذا منصف لأخيك؟
Your brother has been scarred by love.
لقد أصيب أخوك بجرح عميق بسبب الحب.
It's all because of that guy named Lu.
كل ذلك بسبب ذلك الرجل المسمى لو.
It has nothing to do with you or me.
الأمر لا علاقة له بك أو بي.
If you keep messing around with me like this,
إذا استمريت في العبث معي بهذه الطريقة،
I'll go find that Lu guy.
سأذهب لأبحث عن ذلك الرجل المدعو لو.
And get revenge for your brother.
وانتقم لأخيك.
Then everyone can move on.
ثم يمكن للجميع المضي قدماً.
Don't do anything crazy.
لا تفعل أي شيء متهور.
Yi-chen.
يي تشن.
Bro.
أخ.
I brought you your favorite almond cookies.
أحضرت لك كعكات اللوز المفضلة لديك.
Qin Lang was just talking nonsense.
كان تشين لانغ يتحدث هراءً لا معنى له.
He's still drunk.
لا يزال ثملاً.
He'll be good to you.
سيكون لطيفاً معك.
Right, Qin Lang?
صحيح يا تشين لانغ؟
Yichen.
ييتشن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Yi-chen.
يي تشن.
Bro, listen to me.
يا أخي، استمع إليّ.
Don't get upset.
Don't get upset.
Just listen to me first.
Just listen to me first.
Qin Lang and I...
Qin Lang and I...
have always just been friends.
have always just been friends.
We don't have feelings for each other.
We don't have feelings for each other.
That's not true, Bro.
That's not true, Bro.
He likes you.
He likes you.
He'll be good to you.
He'll be good to you.
When did you two meet?
When did you two meet?
From the first day he started working at my bar,
From the first day he started working at my bar,
I knew I liked him.
I knew I liked him.
I know Yi-chen has feelings for me too.
I know Yi-chen has feelings for me too.
But he...
But he...
would never say yes to me.
would never say yes to me.
But I really like Yi-chen.
But I really like Yi-chen.
I like him so, so much.
I like him so, so much.
If you like him, why didn't you say yes?
If you like him, why didn't you say yes?
Is it because of me?
Is it because of me?
Did what happened between me and Lu Feng scare you?
Did what happened between me and Lu Feng scare you?
No, Bro.
No, Bro.
It's not your fault.
It's not your fault.
I'm just... not into guys.
I'm just... not into guys.
It's okay to like him.
It's okay to like him.
Don't go against your own heart.
Don't go against your own heart.
Liking someone is just that.
Liking someone is just that.
It's not perverted.
It's not perverted.
And it's not something you can just give away to someone else.
And it's not something you can just give away to someone else.
Understand?
Understand?
Bro.
Bro.
Why are you so set on working in Lancheng?
Why are you so set on working in Lancheng?
Is it because of us?
Is it because of us?
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
It's because the company in Lancheng...
It's because the company in Lancheng...
offered the best benefits package.
offered the best benefits package.
Then why won't you let us see you off?
Then why won't you let us see you off?
Am I a child? I don't need to be seen off.
Am I a child? I don't need to be seen off.
Besides,
Besides,
Qin Lang has to work during the day,
Qin Lang has to work during the day,
and at the bar at night.
and at the bar at night.
And you,
And you,
you're about to be a junior.
you're about to be a junior.
You should be busy with internships.
You should be busy with internships.
But I...
But I...
Enough with the 'buts'.
Enough with the 'buts'.
Then call me when you get there.
Then call me when you get there.
Okay.
Okay.
(One month later)
(One month later)
(New Employee Information)
(New Employee Information)
Mr. Lu, are we heading home first?
Mr. Lu, are we heading home first?
Straight to the office.
Straight to the office.
Understood.
Understood.
Let's go to the office first.
Let's go to the office first.
Okay.
Okay.
Here he comes, the new boss is here.
Here he comes, the new boss is here.
Good morning, Mr. Lu.
Good morning, Mr. Lu.
Cheng Yichen.
Cheng Yichen.
Long time no see.
Long time no see.
Have a seat.
Have a seat.
Begin.
Begin.
You have a girlfriend?
You have a girlfriend?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I do.
Was it that long-haired girl sitting next to you earlier?
Was it that long-haired girl sitting next to you earlier?
Yes.
Yes.
The handover documents for that project...
The handover documents for that project...
you need to look them over again.
you need to look them over again.
That's enough.
That's enough.
Let's go.
Let's go.
Special Assistant Chou.
Special Assistant Chou.
This proposal...
This proposal...
you don't have make such drastic changes every time.
you don't have make such drastic changes every time.
You can just make some minor changes.
You can just make some minor changes.
Actually,
Actually,
- you need to learn to integrate... - Good morning, Mr. Lu.
- you need to learn to integrate... - Good morning, Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu.
But it just feels like a mess.
But it just feels like a mess.
Right.
Right.
This data...
This data...
Girlfriend?
Girlfriend?
You really got a girlfriend?
You really got a girlfriend?
Chou Cheng.
Chou Cheng.
Bring me Cheng Yichen's file. Now.
Bring me Cheng Yichen's file. Now.
Right away, Mr. Lu.
Right away, Mr. Lu.
Who is it?
Who is it?
Still sleeping at this hour?
Still sleeping at this hour?
I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
When you talk to people in that tone,
When you talk to people in that tone,
it's easy to give them the wrong idea.
it's easy to give them the wrong idea.
Mr. L-
Mr. L-
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu.
If you're free, come over to my place.
If you're free, come over to my place.
I need you to fix my computer.
I need you to fix my computer.
I don't know how to fix computers.
I don't know how to fix computers.
Isn't your major computer-related?
Isn't your major computer-related?
You can't even handle a simple task like this?
You can't even handle a simple task like this?
How did you even get hired at my company?
How did you even get hired at my company?
My major is Digital Media,
My major is Digital Media,
not hardware repair.
not hardware repair.
Just get over here.
Just get over here.
What's the problem?
What's the problem?
We can troubleshoot it online.
We can troubleshoot it online.
My laptop won't turn on.
My laptop won't turn on.
If there are no important files on it,
If there are no important files on it,
then just format the drive.
ثم قم بتهيئة القرص.
I tried.
لقد حاولت.
What does the screen say?
ماذا تقول الشاشة؟
It says 'Cannot format'.
يظهر خطأ "لا يمكن التهيئة".
Okay, find a screwdriver.
حسناً، ابحث عن مفك براغي.
And then?
وثم؟
Flip the back cover over.
اقلب الغلاف الخلفي.
See anything?
هل رأيت أي شيء؟
Describe it.
صفه.
It's smoking.
إنه يدخن.
You better get over here.
من الأفضل أن تأتي إلى هنا.
What's taking so long? Hurry up.
ما الذي يستغرق كل هذا الوقت؟ أسرع.
Stop dawdling.
توقف عن التباطؤ.
Where's the computer?
أين جهاز الكمبيوتر؟
Did water get in it?
هل دخل الماء إليه؟
Can it be fixed?
هل يمكن إصلاحه؟
You should just send it in for repairs.
يجب عليك إرساله للصيانة.
I'll have Chou Cheng come by later.
سأطلب من تشو تشنغ أن يأتي لاحقاً.
Sit down. Have something to drink.
اجلس. تناول شيئاً لتشربه.
This place is decorated pretty nicely.
هذا المكان مزين بشكل جميل للغاية.
My sister used to live here.
كانت أختي تعيش هنا.
I moved in before I even had a chance to clean up.
انتقلت إلى هناك قبل أن تتاح لي حتى فرصة التنظيف.
I should get going.
يجب أن أذهب.
This... this isn't mine.
هذا... هذا ليس ملكي.
It must be my sister's.
لا بد أنها تخص أختي.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
I just moved in a few days ago.
انتقلت إلى هنا قبل بضعة أيام فقط.
It wouldn't be surprising if it were yours.
لن يكون الأمر مفاجئاً إذا كان ملكك.
You have a fiancée, after all.
لديك خطيبة، على كل حال.
Fiancée.
خطيبة.
In another half a month,
بعد نصف شهر آخر،
you'll see
سترى
the news of our broken engagement.
خبر فسخ خطوبتنا.
It was all an act from the beginning.
كان الأمر برمته تمثيلاً منذ البداية.
Everyone knows.
الجميع يعلم.
She needs her dad's business.
إنها بحاجة إلى عمل والدها.
My dad needs her dad's money.
أبي يحتاج إلى مال والدها.
And I...
وأنا...
needed to come back to the country.
كان من الضروري العودة إلى البلاد.
Everyone gets what they want.
يحصل كل شخص على ما يريد.
A win-win-win deal.
صفقة رابحة للجميع.
So... want to think about it?
إذن... هل تريد التفكير في الأمر؟
Th-think about what?
بماذا أفكر؟
Think about...
فكر في...
breaking up with your current girlfriend...
الانفصال عن حبيبتك الحالية...
and getting back together with me.
والعودة إليّ.
I won't mind that you've dated other people.
لن أمانع أنك واعدت أشخاصاً آخرين.
You seem busy. I'll get going.
يبدو أنك مشغول. سأذهب الآن.
Are you too embarrassed to say something?
هل تشعر بالحرج الشديد من قول شيء ما؟
If you are,
إذا كنت كذلك،
I can do it for you.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك من أجلك.
To compensate her,
لتعويضها،
I can even give her a promotion and a raise.
بل يمكنني حتى أن أمنحها ترقية وزيادة في الراتب.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Why don't we grab a bite before you go?
لماذا لا نتناول وجبة خفيفة قبل أن تذهب؟
I'm not hungry.
لست جائعاً.
Well, I am.
حسناً، أنا كذلك.
I'll go change. I'll be quick.
سأذهب لأغير ملابسي. سأكون سريعاً.
Sit.
يجلس.
Don't you dare leave.
إياك أن تغادر.
Order whatever you want.
اطلب ما تشاء.
I'll have this.
سآخذ هذا.
This one.
هذا.
And this one.
وهذا أيضاً.
You're not paying, so what are you afraid of?
أنت لا تدفع، فممّ تخاف؟
I'll eat whatever I want.
سآكل ما أريد.
Bring me a glass of your most expensive red wine.
أحضر لي كأسًا من أغلى أنواع النبيذ الأحمر لديك.
I'll take the wine.
سآخذ النبيذ.
Get him a glass of orange juice.
أحضر له كوباً من عصير البرتقال.
Right away, sir.
حاضر سيدي.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
Cheng Yichen.
تشنغ ييشن.
Mr... Mr. Lu.
السيد... السيد صن.
Come on, eat with us.
هيا، تناول الطعام معنا.
Mr. Lu is treating.
السيد لو هو المعالج.
Waiter.
النادل.
More place settings, please.
المزيد من أدوات المائدة، من فضلك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
He's paying?
هو من سيدفع؟
Here, try this.
جرب هذا.
You've got some on your face.
يوجد بعض منه على وجهك.
Whose girlfriend are you, anyway?
على أي حال، لمن أنتِ حبيبة؟
How dare you, in front of Xiao Chen,
كيف تجرؤ، أمام شياو تشن؟
flirt with another man?
هل تغازل رجلاً آخر؟
I...
أنا...
This is how your girlfriend is acting,
هكذا تتصرف حبيبتك،
and you still don't want to break up with her?
وما زلت لا تريد الانفصال عنها؟
You...
أنت...
You told the boss I'm your girlfriend?
هل أخبرت المدير أنني حبيبتك؟
Don't tell me you've had a secret crush on me...
لا تقل لي إنك معجب بي سراً...
and I just never knew?
ولم أكن أعلم ذلك أبداً؟
Cheng Yichen, you despicable jerk.
تشنغ يي تشن، أيها الأحمق الحقير.
My apologies.
أعتذر.
It seems I've misunderstood.
يبدو أنني أسأت الفهم.
Waiter.
النادل.
The menu.
القائمة.
Well, we'll be going then.
حسنًا، سنذهب إذن.
Let me give you a ride.
دعني أوصلك.
Old classmate.
زميل دراسة قديم.
No, thanks.
ًلا شكرا.
It's on my way.
إنه في طريقي.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
W-well, we're leaving now, Yichen.
حسناً، سنغادر الآن يا ييتشن.
Thanks for dinner, Mr. Lu.
شكراً على العشاء، سيد لو.
Bye-bye. Let's go, let's go.
مع السلامة. هيا بنا، هيا بنا.
Sha-sha.
شرب.
You don't actually like Yichen, do you?
أنت لا تحب ييتشن في الحقيقة، أليس كذلك؟
I'm thirsty.
أنا عطشان.
Let's go to your place for a glass of water.
لنذهب إلى منزلك لنشرب كوباً من الماء.
What?
ماذا؟
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
Xiao Chen, what are you doing?
شياو تشن، ماذا تفعل؟
Is someone in there?
هل يوجد أحد بالداخل؟
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Cheng Yichen.
تشنغ ييشن.
You share this place, right?
أنت تشارك هذا المكان، أليس كذلك؟
It seems nice.
يبدو الأمر جيداً.
Just a little small.
صغير بعض الشيء.
Why don't you live in a nicer apartment?
لماذا لا تسكن في شقة أفضل؟
The rent around here is ridiculously high.
الإيجارات هنا مرتفعة بشكل مبالغ فيه.
For my first year after graduation, living here...
في السنة الأولى بعد التخرج، عشت هنا...
is already pretty good.
جيد جداً بالفعل.
My roommate isn't home much,
زميلي في السكن لا يتواجد في المنزل كثيراً،
so I basically have the place to myself.
لذا، المكان أصبح ملكي وحدي.
What would you like to drink?
ماذا تحب أن تشرب؟
There's no red wine.
لا يوجد نبيذ أحمر.
I'd like...
أود أن...
orange juice.
عصير البرتقال.
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
How about...
ماذا عن...
we watch a movie?
هل نشاهد فيلماً؟
- You... - I haven't seen a movie in a long time.
- أنت... - لم أشاهد فيلماً منذ فترة طويلة.
Aren't you... busy?
ألا تكون مشغولاً؟
I was planning on taking a break today anyway.
كنت أخطط لأخذ استراحة اليوم على أي حال.
Not sentimental at all.
ليس عاطفياً على الإطلاق.
Truly the work of a master.
عملٌ بارعٌ حقاً.
The more the audience suffers,
كلما زادت معاناة الجمهور،
the colder the camera becomes.
كلما زادت برودة الكاميرا.
True suffering...
معاناة حقيقية...
is something you can't even put into words.
إنه شيء لا يمكن وصفه بالكلمات.